// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Does your child learns new words slowly?",
    answer: "moreoften" || "sometimes",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },

  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "Is your child having problem in remembering or naming letters, numbers and colors?",
    answer: "sometimes" || "moreoften",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Is your child reading well below the expected level for age?",
    answer: "moreoften" || "sometimes",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "Is your child having difficulty in finding the right word or forming answers to questions?",
    answer: "sometimes" || "moreoften",

    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Does your child avoids activities that involve reading?",
    answer: "moreoften" || "sometimes",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "Is your child having ability to sound out the pronunciation of an unfamiliar word?",
    answer: "never" || "lessoften",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Does your child remembers the sequence of things?",
    answer: "lessoften" || "never",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Is your child doing math word problems easily?",
    answer: "never" || "lessoften",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Is your child able to summarize a story perfectly?",
    answer: "lessoften" || "never",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "Is your child having Slow and labor-intensive reading and writing?",
    answer: "sometimes" || "moreoften",
    options: ["never", "lessoften", "sometimes", "moreoften"],
  },
];
